{
    "subject": "resource/Kunming\u2013Singapore_Railway",
    "predicate": "property/linelengthKm",
    "object": "3900",
    "human_readable": "The length of the Kunming\u2013Singapore Railway is 3900 kilometers.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9075437784194946,
            "question": "What is the length of the Kunming\u2013Singapore Railway?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8509194254875183,
            "question": "In kilometers, what distance does the Kunming\u2013Singapore Railway cover?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8086802363395691,
            "question": "How long is the railway route between Kunming and Singapore?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7607967257499695,
            "question": "What unit of measurement is used for the length of the Kunming\u2013Singapore Railway?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7354550957679749,
            "question": "Could you compare the length of the Kunming\u2013Singapore Railway to another famous railway line?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6639922261238098,
            "question": "Is the Kunming\u2013Singapore Railway a long railway line?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6430588960647583,
            "question": "How long would it take to travel by train from Kunming to Singapore on the new railway?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.36571869254112244,
            "question": "What is the significance of connecting Kunming and Singapore with a railway?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.23208697140216827,
            "question": "What are some potential challenges associated with building a railway of this length?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.21566718816757202,
            "question": "What economic benefits might arise from the construction of the Kunming\u2013Singapore Railway?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The length of the Kunming\u2013Singapore Railway is 3900 kilometers.",
            "html": "dbpedia_1603_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some potential challenges associated with building a railway of this length?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1603_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the significance of connecting Kunming and Singapore with a railway?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1603_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How long would it take to travel by train from Kunming to Singapore on the new railway?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1603_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1603_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1603_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1603_113.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1603_122.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1603_132.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1603_59.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1603_69.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1603_81.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1603_88.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1603_91.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n``` \n\n\nThe documents state that the Singapore-Kunming Rail Link (SKRL) is 6,617.5km-long.  Therefore, the statement that it's 3900 kilometers long is incorrect. \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "Based on the provided context information, here is the evaluation of the triple:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nThe reason for this answer is that according to document file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_1603/re-ranker-msmarco/11.txt, the length of the Singapore-Kunming Rail Link (SKRL) is mentioned as 6,617.5km-long, which is much longer than 3900 kilometers."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n```\n\nThe documents provided do not contain specific information about the exact length of the Kunming\u2013Singapore Railway. While details are given about various segments and parts of the railway network, no document mentions a total length of 3900 kilometers for this particular railway line."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"no\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 0,
    "actual_decision": 0,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}